PRINCIPAL POLICY OF THE FOUNDATION PROJECT
SERVING AS THE WORKING POLICY OF MR LI AO
==========================================

PART I. PREFACE

This document outlines the most fundamental, principal policies of The Foundation Project, serving as the principal policy of Li Ao applying to almost every his conducts. He aimed to gradually expanding the applipability to every of his conducts in the future.

PART II. POLICY

1.	Every conducts of Li Ao must be carried out in an ethical way, not in contradiction with any civilisation of any human society.

2.	No conducts of Li Ao shall be carried out in violation of any ethical values of any civilisation of any human society in any part of the world.

3.	In order to carry out retaliatory activities, no revenges shall be occurred which hurts any innocent parties in any forms. Additionally, such revenge activities must not exceed the intensity of the degree of necessity.

4.	In an event where Li Ao is in a position of solving sophisticated problems, and such resolve of such problems must involve hurts of innocent parties where they should not be hurt, assessments must be carried out to ensure ethical carry out of such kind of activities, and in case it's found in violation of any ethical values of any civilisation of human society, such activities must be unconditonally halted or aborted. As a general rule, the outcome of resolve of such problems must include the benefits of the human society, or Li Ao should not accept to intervene into the situation.

5.	In an event may Li Ao's conducts and other kinds of activities have caused hurt to innocent parties for which the parties should not sustain the hurt, Li Ao must compensate to anyone involved in the event that sustained loss of any degree.

6.	Any conducts of Li Ao must honour the dignity of anyone; no conducts of Li Ao may hurt the dignity of any person.

7.	Li Ao must not carry out any activities that he is not in a position to do so, which will involve hurts of any innocent parties of any kind and any degree, for any reason.

8. 	Li Ao must train himself or accept training from another party to ensure he become trainned to be able to voluntary guarantee commiting the principle policy set out in this document.

9.	In the event may situation change, Li Ao will amend the principal policy, however ethical values must not be violated in any form with any excuse.

10.	Li Ao must deny alignment of any communism ideology of any kinds in any form. Similarly, he must deny alignment of any wrongful ideology of any religions of any kinds in any form.

11.	As a general rule, any business activities of Li Ao must honour good local customs of commencement of such activities. Local languages may be used in addition to official languages in honour of such good local customs.

12.	(a) The official working language of Li Ao is the British and American variant of English. Unless necessary, no communication languages may replace the official status of the prescribed variants of English.

	(b) Li Ao must not promote the mono dominance of Chinese use in the society of the People's Republic of China. Similarly, Li Ao promote the gradual adoption of English use in the Chinese society.

13.	

