====================
Types of Documentation
====================


I. GENERAL PRINCIPLES

The types of documentation composed or constructed by Li Ao includes those made with conventional principles, this includes documents written in forms that are normally well-recognised and used by people or within a particular industry. They also include those that are constructed with Li Ao's own ways which cannot be read or understood with general, conventional knowledge, or which are not constructed in a de facto regular format, including by using Li Ao's own ways of construction, however, can be identified with conventional knowledge that such contents are in a special, proprietary format that should be read with other ways.

Documentation should have its manifests of internal use must also be identifiable by being read with conventional means, unless such documentation is for internal use that doesn't face to the public or others who fall outside of the internal use scenario.

Whenever possible standardised instead of non-standardised documentation should be constructed in order to be able to achieve the best performance and effects, however non-standardised documentation is also not discouraged if such standardised form is unviable or unnecessary.

An array of different types of documentation would be designed by time. In the future may one type of documentation can be constructed in an uniform way following certain templates, or even based on that, be able to be constructed in a special, internal use format that can both save time and resources, and even possibly to a matured degree, be read by computerised programs, the documentation of methodology of constructing such kind of documents should be documented well for the sake of ensuring quality of documents created under such methodology. Li Ao project that the eventual development of these documenting methodologies of every type of documents will realise this final goal as they construct those machine-readable documents precisely, correctly, efficiently, and state-of-the-art.


II. Types of Documentation

Categorising by nature, all types of documentataion can fall under the following categories:--

	a. Subjective Fact Documentation (type code G) -- a type of documentation which documents subjective fact, including factual information of a particular object, event, person, location, species of animals, type of computer programs, etc.;

	b. Event Trail Documentation (type code H) -- a type of documentation which documents an event with the aim of documenting key particulars of it in order to reserve trails for later references;

	c. Mixed Purpose Documentation -- a type of documentation which documents information of differnet kinds that both Subjective Fact Documentation and Event Trail Documentation covers.

There are currently the following types of documentation, categorised by intended usage:--

	a. General Subjective Fact Documentation (type code A) -- a type of documentation which is of the kind Subjective Fact Documentation, however is hard to be categorised into any other particular document type at the current time;

	b. General Event Trail Documentation (type code B) -- a type of documentation which is of the kind Event Trail Documentation, however is hard to be categorised into any other particular document type at the current time;

	c. Object Information Documentation (type code C) -- a type of documentation which can fall under both the category Subjective Fact Documentation and Event Trail Documentation, or falls under the category Mixed Purpose Documentation, judging its intended purpose, for which they  document information including the particulars and other kinds of one or multiple particular objects, of which they include material objects that exists physically, electronic records that they are considered objects and conceptual object which exists as a particular concept, and their existence are generally be able to be annotated by an object identifier under Li Ao's object-level abstraction model;

	d. Object Relationships Documentation (type code D) -- a type of documentation which falls under the category Subjective Fact Documentation, that documents the relationships of objects that can be classified as objects under Li Ao's object-level abstraction model;

	e. Object Journey Documentation (type code E) -- a type of documentation which falls under the category Subjective Fact Documentation, that documents the journey of objects to changing their particulars that they no longer be subjected to the original objects but is subject to new objects for which by the given situations they have actually changed their basic particulars that classify them as individual objects (for example, an ice becoming malted, or an insect being dissected; note that, for example, information documenting a computer unit as an object that are dismantled into multiple parts are considered journey of this object to no longer being an original object, however information documenting such a computer unit being dismantled and assembled again should be considered 2 piece of information that fall under such subject, with one part documenting the journey of the system unit to 'disappear' and another part documenting the journey of multiple system parts coming together to make the unit 'reappear';

	f. 
