GENERAL PROVISIONS OF QUALITY CONTROL MEASURES AND ETHICS PRINCIPLES
OF WORKS CARRIED ON BY LI AO UNDER THE FRAMEWORK OF WORKS GOVERNANCE
SET FORTH IN THE FOUNDATION PROJECT
====================================================================

I. Quality Control Measures

The quality control measures (QA measures) should be taken in order to ensure the quality of works carried out under the frameworks of works governance set forth in The Foundation Project ("the Frameworks"). As a mandate, such measures must be carried out when quality control is needed throughout every steps of conducting works that are regulated under this Project.

Under no situations should the QA measures not be carried out on works that are governed by the framework of The Foundation Project; similarly, under no circumstances should simplified QA measures, whereas not being permitted under principles and rules of the Frammework, or neglected QA measures, on all occasions, be carried out in order to fulfill the requirements of quality assurance of the Framework.

The QA measures should use tools, utilities, and other material means, with correct methodologies to ensure concrete works are carried out, or, if applicable, the QA measures could use correct methodologies without the need of utilising tools, utilities, and other material means, on occasions may the use of material means are unnecessary and implausible.

The Framework prescribes operational rules to carry out QA measures, and on the enforcement of quality assuance that must be applied to the applicable works. These rules can be general provisions that must be specified into concrete details by subsidiary rules, for which such subsidiary rules are beyond the scope of the Framework.

QA measures must be taken, whether on a broader range covering an array of works carried out under the Framework or on individual works of this kind, in a timely manner, for the sake of ensuring the ethical effects of such kind of works. QA measures for these ethics evaluations must not be deterred or deferred beyond a reasonable timeframe unless extraordinary circumstances exist which forcifully halts or aborts such works to be carried out.

II. Ethics Principles

Under no circumstances should any works be carried out under the Framework violate any ethics principles of any civilization in any physical location; this does not include historical civilization that are not considered applicable to the modern society, and those uncivilised civiliazation existed as a concept for special purposes. Li Ao works actively to ensure in the future, every conducts of him personally carried out must ensure compliance of ethics principles of this Framework.


